Contact

8826962919 (Mobile) hs20238@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ creativehimanshu00 (LinkedIn) coder-himanshu.github.io/Portfolio (Portfolio) www.techfreez.co.in (Blog)

Top Skills

CSS

HTML5

Angular 6

Languages

Hindi (Full Professional)

English (Professional Working)

Punjabi (Elementary)

Certifications

Concept Course On Computer
Wire framing with balsamiq mockups
Color Theory & Responsive Web
Designing
HTML & CSS Foundation

Object Oriented Programming C & C ++

Himanshu Sharma

Front End Developer || HTML5 || CSS3 || JavaScript|| Bootstrap || UI/ UX Designing || JQuery || MongoDB ||Angular 6

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Summary

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in web development as well as Graphic's Designing. Skilled in Web Applications and video editing. Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Angular6, NodeJS (Basics), MongoDB, HTML5, JavaScript, JQuery . Strong engineering professional with Front-End Development and focused in Computer Science from National Institute of Information Technology.

Experience

Tata Consultancy Services
Programmer
July 2017 - Present
Gurgaon, India

Navrang...Colours of India Web Developer February 2017 - April 2017 (3 months) New Delhi Area, India

Education

National Institute of Information Technology
.Net Development , Computer Science · (2016 - 2017)

Chatrapati Sahuji Maharaj Kanpur University, Kanpur Bachelor of Computer Application, Computer Science (2013 - 2016)